http://semen-detection.com/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Is your woman is cheating on you? Is your man is cheating on you?
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm and saliva.
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another male.
Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets, feminine pad, panty liner and paper towels.
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm, saliva and menstrual blood.
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another female. Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets and paper towels.With over 3400 completed tests, SSDI promises the most accurate, sensitive, and comprehensive laboratory test available...
All within one business day of sample receipt! Call today 844-441-8610 or click on Order Now to order online.Learn More Order Now
Semen Sperm and Saliva Detection! Over 3400 Completed Tests... 844-441-8610 Toll Free and Confidential
With over 3400 completed tests, SSDI promises the most accurate, sensitive, and comprehensive laboratory test available...
All within one business day of sample receipt! Call today 844-441-8610 or click on Order Now to order online.Learn More Order Now
If you think your man is cheating on you...
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm, saliva and menstrual blood. We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another female.Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets and paper towels.Learn More Order Now
If you think your woman is cheating on you...
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm and saliva
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another male. Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets, feminine pad, panty liner and paper towels.Learn More Order Now
Home Test Kits for only $39.95 plus shipping...
SSDI (Semen Sperm Saliva Detection) offers home test kits for seminal fluid, saliva, blood and menstrual blood for $39.95 plus shipping. We always recommend that samples tested at home are confirmed with a lab serology test before any accusations or life changing decisions are made.Learn More Order Now
›
‹
1
2
3
4
5
Privacy Policy
Semen and Sperm Detection (SSDI) Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Statement
SSDI  values the privacy of our visitors/customers and takes every known precaution to safe guard the information we collect from unauthorized use.  The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for SSDI.
Your personal information with results will never be provided to a third party without your written permission.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
SSDI believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site.  We employ various methods for collecting information.  To begin with, we use “cookies” that are needed to compile aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our web site. Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you, such as credit card numbers, bank accounts, social security numbers, home address, email address and the like.  This is the type of information that most people consider private and deem the most important to protect from unauthorized access.  Non-personally identifiable information most often consists of things such as your search preferences, the types of products you have bought, how many times you have visited a particular web site, etc. This type of information is usually associated with a particular computer or IP address but not with a particular person. “Cookies” are pieces of information generated by a Web server and stored in the user’s computer, ready for future access.
SSDI watches and reviews your visits to determine how to guide you through our websites.  This information includes your IP address, country, state, and city, how many times you have visited, how many pages you review, what pages you review, and how long you remain on each page.
If a person or company continues to visit our website through access by our “pay per click” keywords, their access is permanently denied.
WHY DO WE COLLECT THIS INFORMATION?
We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers and to reduce our marketing costs.  We need to know who you are in order to verify the credit card information you have sent us.  We collect several pieces of personal information from you in order to complete this verification process.  The non-personal information that we collect from you is used in order to offer you better service and to make your experience with our site more enjoyable.  Any information that we may inadvertently collect from you, that does not serve one of these reasons stated above, is immediately purged from our system.
HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION PROTECTED?
We use the latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception.  We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas.  We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds.  All employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities.  We also have back up servers and power supplies to guard against power outages and other natural occurrences that could pose a threat to the integrity of your personal information.  Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account.  Once an account has been terminated, measures are taken to remove those users from the system who no longer need access to our system. When an employee is terminated or is no longer with the company, we change the access codes that the employee used to access any customer accounts.  Passwords must contain at least six characters, one of which is nonalphanumeric.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?
Only those employees that are responsible for handling your account have access to your information.  Additionally, employees in our technical department may have access to your information in order to conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and in order to perform necessary maintenance work.  In order to process your credit card we have to consult with an out side credit card processing company.  These processing companies are regulated by the banking industry and must meet certain security requirements in order to be in business.  The processing companies will have access to your credit card information, billing address, name, and possibly your telephone number.  The processing company will communicate with the issuing bank of your credit card in order to get final approval to charge your credit card for the product or services we are providing for you.  Should you choose to receive additional information regarding one of our services or products, we may pass your email address to one of our partners who offers similar products or services that you might be interested in.  Additionally, judicial requests by a duly authorized court will require us to divulge certain information regarding your account should that situation arise.  Finally, should our company ever be bought or sold, your account information would then become the property of the new owner/entity.
CAN I CORRECT OR REMOVE INFORMATION FROM YOUR SITE?
You always have the option to view your account to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct.  You also have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private.  However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service or products you have requested.  We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you.
CAN I OPT OUT OF HAVING CERTAIN INFORMATION COLLECTED?
You have the option of disabling your computer’s ability to accept or transmit cookies or use an IP address hiding program. This will prevent us from gathering certain non-personally identifiable information from you.
NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.  However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented.  We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes.  Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally.  You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate.
Easy 3 Step Process
1. Order your serology test by credit card, PayPal or money order.
2. Please ship the garment or item to be tested in a paper bag or envelope. On the outside of the paper bag or envelope, write your contact information and date you obtained the sample. Please DO NOT use a mailer or poly / plastic bag or wrapping around the garment, as this may cause the item to sweat and destroy the sample.
3. Send sample to SSDI, 110 East Broward Blvd. Suite 1700 Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33301 in envelope or paper bag.
Contact SSDI
Ordering: 844-441-8610
Email: Info@Semen-Detection.com
Mailing Address: SSDI, 110 East Broward Blvd. Suite 1700 Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33301
For Infidelity and Sexual Assault
Semen and Sperm Detection, Inc. provides 100% accurate and conclusive analysis for the detection of semen, sperm, and human saliva (and blood if applicable) to determine whether infidelity or rape has occurred. Our 4-phase testing process is the most accurate and reliable semen and saliva detection test available. A comprehensive written report is provided for each case, including photographic documentation. Tests are typically completed within one business day from receipt of the sample(s).
Default
Title
Date
Random
+Read More
Read More
+Read More
Read More
+Read More
Read More
Is your woman is cheating on you? Is your man is cheating on you?
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm and saliva.
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another male.
Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets, feminine pad, panty liner and paper towels.
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm, saliva and menstrual blood.
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another female. Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets and paper towels.With over 3400 completed tests, SSDI promises the most accurate, sensitive, and comprehensive laboratory test available...
All within one business day of sample receipt! Call today 844-441-8610 or click on Order Now to order online.Learn More Order Now
Semen Sperm and Saliva Detection! Over 3400 Completed Tests... 844-441-8610 Toll Free and Confidential
With over 3400 completed tests, SSDI promises the most accurate, sensitive, and comprehensive laboratory test available...
All within one business day of sample receipt! Call today 844-441-8610 or click on Order Now to order online.Learn More Order Now
If you think your man is cheating on you...
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm, saliva and menstrual blood. We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another female.Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets and paper towels.Learn More Order Now
If you think your woman is cheating on you...
What we can test for: Seminal fluid, sperm and saliva
We can determine if the sample/stain belongs to you or to another male. Items that can be tested: t-shirts, pants, underwear, used condoms, tissues, bed sheets, feminine pad, panty liner and paper towels.Learn More Order Now
Home Test Kits for only $39.95 plus shipping...
SSDI (Semen Sperm Saliva Detection) offers home test kits for seminal fluid, saliva, blood and menstrual blood for $39.95 plus shipping. We always recommend that samples tested at home are confirmed with a lab serology test before any accusations or life changing decisions are made.Learn More Order Now
›
‹
1
2
3
4
5
Additional Testing
Maternity Test Kits Most Common Reasons for Maternity Testing - Immigration, Adopted Child, Suspected Baby Switch, In Vitro fertilization
Paternity TestingThe kit includes swabs for the mother and alleged father. Results typically take 7 business days.
Infidelity TestingTesting for Infidelity detecting sperm, semen, saliva and blood.
Legal Chain of Custody DNAHome Test Kit – With Chain of Custody Paperwork. Can be admissible in court if instructions are properly followed.
Legal Chain of Custody InfidelityHome Test Kit – With Chain of Custody Paperwork. Can be admissible in court if instructions are properly followed.
Immigration DNA TestingNo hassle flat fee pricing, No hidden shipping costs, No hidden collection fees,
Forensic AnalysisDNA, Serology, Crime Scene Reconstruction, Forgery Examination, Ink Dating, Computer and Cell Phone Forensics
AP Semen Detection Test KitsAcid Phosphatase is an enzyme secreted by the prostate gland that is present in large amounts in seminal fluid.
Services
Immigration DNA Testing DNA Testing. US Embassy and USCIS Letter for Immigration immigrationdnatesting.us
Semen and Sperm Detection Semen Sperm Saliva and Blood Detection Testing semen-detection.com
Forensic Investigation DNA Serology Fingerprint Ink Dating Crime Scene Investigation and Fraud 4n6.com
Copyright 2017 SSDI, Inc..
Top
Accredited Testing Laboratories In These States
AlabamaArizonaAlaskaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgia
HawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMaryland
MassachusettsMIchiganMinnesotaMissouriMississippiMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew Jersey
New MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth Carolina
South DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginaWisconsinWyoming
